<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Committee on New College MCR</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Committee on New College MCR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>James &#39;Theo&#39; McAuliffe (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/1-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/1-president/</guid>
      <description>Theo is a DPhil student on the Interdisciplinary Biosciences DTP, focusing on virology related research. To break up the monotony of living in a lab he enjoys running, playing rugby and football, sleeping and watching trash TV. Get in touch if you have any ideas to improve MCR life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitzroy &#39;Pablo&#39; Wickham (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/2-vice-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/2-vice-president/</guid>
      <description>Pablo hails from Jamaica and is currently reading for a DPhil in Clinical Neuroscience. When he isn&amp;rsquo;t tending to his MCR Veep responsibilities Pablo enjoys cooking, eating, working out, acting and binging Netflix series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mikhail &#39;Misha&#39; Vaganov (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/3-treasurer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/3-treasurer/</guid>
      <description>I am doing a DPhil in experimental Condensed Matter Physics. Most of the time I spend in the lab kicking electron and nuclear spins trying to make them behave and be coherent. This is motivated mostly by the appalling hardware requirements for Elden ring, Final fantasy and God of War: humans definitely need quantum computers for those games!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bushra Senin (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/4-social-sec1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/4-social-sec1/</guid>
      <description>Bushra is pursuing a DPhil in Biochemistry, focusing on DNA replication and repair mechanisms. Apart from complaining about how long her day has been (every day), she spends her free time reading and attempting to write poetry and playing the piano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Morgan (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/5-social-sec2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/5-social-sec2/</guid>
      <description>George is doing a DPhil in Condensed Matter Physics exploring new materials for next generation solar cells and has moved to Oxford after completing his undergraduate degree at Imperial College London. He enjoys spending time with friends, playing rugby (for both New College and the University), and making the most of our time here in the MCR at New College.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emma Kerry</title>
      <link>/team/6-welfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/6-welfare/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nika Vahcic (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/7-house-officer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/7-house-officer/</guid>
      <description>Nika is doing an MPhil in Economics. She plays violin and occasionally wakes up at 6am to go to rowing outings. Reach out to her if you have any requests/ideas for additions to our MCR spaces!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eloise Knight-Smith</title>
      <link>/team/8-bar-rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/8-bar-rep/</guid>
      <description>Eloise is currently reading for an MPhil in Greek Literature and Language. Some of you may know them from their tenure as LGBTQ+ rep, but they&amp;rsquo;re now back and better than ever with much more alcohol at their disposal (and some fancy soft drinks too)- you will likely find them frantically writing essays behind the bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mandisa Shandu (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/9-ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/9-ed/</guid>
      <description>Mandisa is from South Africa and is doing a DPhil in Law. She enjoys jazz, poetry, long walks (not runs!) and wine. Feel free to reach out about any ideas you may have to make your experience at New more inclusive, or to celebrate your culture/identity as a college community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aidan Manley (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/10-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/10-sports/</guid>
      <description>Aidan is a DPhil in Chemistry. When not wondering why his code has inexplicably produced imaginary numbers, he is usually waking up at dawn for rowing outings, kicking a football against a wall while reminding himself of Einstein’s definition of insanity or sobbing over Newcastle United’s most recent result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kristen Koopmans (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/11-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/11-women/</guid>
      <description>Kristen (she/her) is currently pursuing a DPhil in Cancer Sciences. When she’s not pipetting things in the lab, she’s probably cafe hopping trying to find the best cortado in Oxford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mia Zipperle (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/11b-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/11b-women/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I’m Mia! I’m from Heidelberg, Germany, and am currently doing an MSt in German Literature. When I’m not stuck reading 19th century novels in the library, I can either be found baking for my housemates, spending all of my money on coffee, walking through Oxford&amp;rsquo;s parks or queuing at Najar’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mizy Judah Clifton (he/they)</title>
      <link>/team/12-lgbtiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/12-lgbtiq/</guid>
      <description>Mizy is reading for an MSt in Women&amp;rsquo;s, Gender, and Sexuality Studies. When he&amp;rsquo;s not reading wacky queer/trans theory, he can be found asleep (with a philosophy podcast playing in the background) or out on a long walk. Mizy&amp;rsquo;s main goal is to create a safe and supportive environment for LGBTQ+ people at NC and is always available for a chat–very little phases him, so do reach out if you ever need a listening ear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabriel &#39;Gabi&#39; Abrahams (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/13-bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/13-bike/</guid>
      <description>Gabi is a DPhil student in the Interdisciplinary Biosciences DTP, with undergraduate and masters degrees in physics (the experimental kind, so your bike may emit strange radiation after he&amp;rsquo;s done with it). As bike rep he maintains the MCR’s fleet of bicycles which are free for members to borrow. If you have a bike problem, feel free to ask for tips!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hazel Simpson (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/14b-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/14b-arts/</guid>
      <description>Hazel is doing an MSc in Experimental Psychology. She loves cooking, reading, and drawing. A typical day-in-the-life might involve working (unproductively) in one of Oxford’s many libraries, laying in bed contemplating life, and then rushing to an event she forgot she signed up for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mhairi Carson (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/14-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/14-arts/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m keen to organise lots of events and activities that are easily accessible to everyone in the MCR and collaborate with other colleges so that we can all meet new people, whilst strengthening our own NC community. I&amp;rsquo;m studying musicology and spend my free time playing the trumpet as one sixth of catbandcat!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cieran Leigh (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/15-disability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/15-disability/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Cieran, a mathematics teacher (PGCE) at the Department of Education, and the first generation to come to university in my family. I&amp;rsquo;m a disabled student and come from a family with a long history of disabled family members and supporting disabled chairites. My interest include recreational mathematics, sailing, and supporting the Welsh rugby team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>