<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Committee on New College MCR</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Committee on New College MCR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>James &#39;Theo&#39; McAuliffe (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/1-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/1-president/</guid>
      <description>Theo is a DPhil student on the Interdisciplinary Biosciences DTP, focusing on virology related research. To break up the monotony of living in a lab he enjoys running, playing rugby and football, sleeping and watching trash TV. Get in touch if you have any ideas to improve MCR life!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitzroy &#39;Pablo&#39; Wickham (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/2-vice-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/2-vice-president/</guid>
      <description>Pablo hails from Jamaica and is currently reading for a DPhil in Clinical Neuroscience. When he isn&amp;rsquo;t tending to his MCR Veep responsibilities Pablo enjoys cooking, eating, working out, acting and binging Netflix series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mikhail &#39;Misha&#39; Vaganov (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/3-treasurer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/3-treasurer/</guid>
      <description>I am doing a DPhil in experimental Condensed Matter Physics. Most of the time I spend in the lab kicking electron and nuclear spins trying to make them behave and be coherent. This is motivated mostly by the appalling hardware requirements for Elden ring, Final fantasy and God of War: humans definitely need quantum computers for those games!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bushra Senin (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/4-social-sec1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/4-social-sec1/</guid>
      <description>Bushra is pursuing a DPhil in Biochemistry, focusing on DNA replication and repair mechanisms. Apart from complaining about how long her day has been (every day), she spends her free time reading and attempting to write poetry and playing the piano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Morgan (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/5-social-sec2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/5-social-sec2/</guid>
      <description>George is doing a DPhil in Condensed Matter Physics exploring new materials for next generation solar cells and has moved to Oxford after completing his undergraduate degree at Imperial College London. He enjoys spending time with friends, playing rugby (for both New College and the University), and making the most of our time here in the MCR at New College.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Arndt (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/6-welfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/6-welfare/</guid>
      <description>Nick is from Germany and currently reading for an MPhil in International Relations at the DPIR, just across from the Weston Buildings. He completed his undergrad at in Groningen, the Netherlands. Next to studying, he enjoys playing and watching football, wasting money on fancy coffee, and cooking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nika Vahcic (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/7-house-officer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/7-house-officer/</guid>
      <description>Nika is doing an MPhil in Economics. She plays violin and occasionally wakes up at 6am to go to rowing outings. Reach out to her if you have any requests/ideas for additions to our MCR spaces!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alysia Martinez</title>
      <link>/team/8b-bar-rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/8b-bar-rep/</guid>
      <description>Howdy y’all ! my name&amp;rsquo;s Alysia (uh-lee-see-yuh) and I hail from the great state of Texas and a cute lil city called Dallas. I’m a first year MSc studying Experimental Therapeutics (i.e. clinical trials) and I’m very excited for this year and feel privileged to serve such an incredible group of people (:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eloise Knight-Smith</title>
      <link>/team/8-bar-rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/8-bar-rep/</guid>
      <description>Eloise is currently reading for an MPhil in Greek Literature and Language. Some of you may know them from their tenure as LGBTQ+ rep, but they&amp;rsquo;re now back and better than ever with much more alcohol at their disposal (and some fancy soft drinks too)- you will likely find them frantically writing essays behind the bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Han Zhao (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/9-ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/9-ed/</guid>
      <description>Hi y’all! My name is Han, and I am the E&amp;amp;D Rep for the New College MCR. I grew up in the USA in the suburbs of Dallas, TX, and I did my undergrad at UCLA. Right now, I’m pursuing an MSc in Statistical Science. Outside of academics, I love playing chess and watching nature documentaries. (Planet Earth III is out now!!)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gregory Langone</title>
      <link>/team/10-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/10-sports/</guid>
      <description>Greg is a Civil Engineering student from New York. He specializes in getting evicted from sports grounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miriam Yakobashvili (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/11-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/11-women/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Miriam. I am from Tbilisi Georgia, and doing an MPhil in International Relations. Outside of my studies, I enjoy art, cooking, and trying out new cuisines. I wish to make the MCR a safer and more inclusive space for all! Please reach out with any ideas or concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elena Russo (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/12-lgbtiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/12-lgbtiq/</guid>
      <description>Elena is currently doing my DPhil in History. She likes to spend my days immersed in history books among dusty library shelves, but you will also find me on a football pitch or playing the violin (or at least trying to!). As LGBTQ+ officer, she aims to create a community where everyone can feel at home in shared spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Selfe (he/him)</title>
      <link>/team/13-bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/13-bike/</guid>
      <description>I have just begun a DPhil, focusing on neuroscience. I am from South Africa and enjoy all things outdoors, including biking!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frankie Lukens</title>
      <link>/team/14b-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/14b-arts/</guid>
      <description>Frankie is a Florida Man (and also Guatemalan). He is doing an MSt in Modern European History. When not reading about the German-Latin American coffee trade, he enjoys swimming, eating Thai and Indian food, learning German, and going to pubs with friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marie-Angela Stokolosa (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/14-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/14-arts/</guid>
      <description>Hi ! I&amp;rsquo;m Marie-Angela and I&amp;rsquo;m studying for the Diploma in Legal Studies. I previously studied in London and in Paris. I enjoy oil painting and life drawing and I’m very proud of my growing collection of ugly mugs. My goal this year is to fill up the many sketchbooks I brought from home and to eat 11 hashbrowns in one sitting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Lovell (they/them)</title>
      <link>/team/15-disability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/15-disability/</guid>
      <description>I’m a PGCE student and I specialise in History. For my undergraduate degree, I researched and wrote about the disability rights movement under Margaret Thatcher’s governments. I am a first generation and estranged student. I have previously worked on the first Global Ministerial Mental Health Event, and with the Children’s Society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lara Boudinot (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/16-environmental/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/16-environmental/</guid>
      <description>Lara is pursuing a DPhil in Biology focusing on large mammals in Uganda. When she is not explaining to everyone why the Packers and Bucks are the best American sports teams or confessing her love for cheese, you can find her hiking, cooking, or playing volleyball!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumedha Nalluru (she/her)</title>
      <link>/team/16b-environmental/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/16b-environmental/</guid>
      <description>Sumedha is pursuing a DPhil in Clinical Neurosciences, focusing on learning and memory in healthy and psychosis conditions. She enjoys doing art, baking, racquet sports, running and playing board games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zachary &#39;Zach&#39; Resatar</title>
      <link>/team/17-freshers-rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/17-freshers-rep/</guid>
      <description>Zach is pursuing an MSc in Higher Education with a focus on American educational policy. He was born and raised in Ohio, but he is not unfamiliar with Oxford as he completed his undergrad at Miami University (the Paris of the Midwest). In his free time, he enjoys wine, food, and sports, and if you combine all three it&amp;rsquo;s probably the best day of his life (repeatable).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjun Parcasio</title>
      <link>/team/18-students-rep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/18-students-rep/</guid>
      <description>Marjun is reading for a MSc in International Human Rights Law. In his non-Oxford life, Marjun practises law as a litigator in London, but you’ll otherwise find him drinking his eighth coffee of the day, causing havoc while coxing on the river or going for long runs to ruminate over why he thought that juggling a full-time job with a part-time degree was a good idea.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
