<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>College Life on New College MCR</title>
    <link>/college/</link>
    <description>Recent content in College Life on New College MCR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/college/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Housing</title>
      <link>/college/housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/college/housing/</guid>
      <description>New College typically accommodates most of its graduates for their first year, with a reasonable chance of a second year in college accommodation. In particular, non-UK graduates will almost always be housed in college accommodation for their first year. Oxford University graduates are not guaranteed accommodation in college but will often still be offered housing for their first year.
Living in college Weston buildings Graduate Housing Ballot Weston Lodge Living in college New College has graduate accommodation at the Weston Buildings site on St.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food</title>
      <link>/college/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/college/food/</guid>
      <description>New College has not only a great dining hall, but also a wonderful kitchen that caters to any dietary restriction.
Eating in College Dinner and Formals High Table Dining Rights Eating Elsewhere Eating in College Food is available to graduates during term time; all meals are charged to your till account and paid for using your Bod-card.
Breakfast: Breakfast is available from 8 am to 9 am. A choice of an English cooked breakfast, continental breakfast, cereal etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic Life</title>
      <link>/college/academic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/college/academic/</guid>
      <description>New College supports a lovely, tranquil environment for students of many disciplines. No matter your learning style or pursuit in life, you will find inspiration in the cloisters or dining halls when not in our library of rich history and knowledge.
Library services Suspension Library services Library Opening Hours
All year: 8 am to 2:00 am (every day)
To suggest new books for the Library, contact the Librarian, Dr Christopher Skelton-Foord</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health</title>
      <link>/college/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/college/health/</guid>
      <description>New College is dedicated to ensuring your health needs are fulfilled. The MCR, College, and (for the most part) NHS have your back.
Table of Contents
College Doctors College Nurse College Dentist Sexual Health Useful links related to Health College Doctors New College requires all students to register with an Oxford doctor. The College Doctors, Dr John Sichel and Dr Diana Ferguson, will accept any member of College who wishes to register with them under the NHS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication</title>
      <link>/college/communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/college/communication/</guid>
      <description>Coming to a new place and making new friends requires a way to communicate, which these days mostly happens via the internet.
Email College Emails Social Events Emails Teams Internet Access Email College Emails As part of the MCR you will be added to the college run email list new-mcr@corelli.new.ox.ac.uk. Messages from the college list will have a subject line that starts with [New-MCR] and will general be announcements from the SCR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaces in College</title>
      <link>/college/spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>/college/spaces/</guid>
      <description>The main site of college is beautiful, and offers many places to exist and enjoy, as well as various music facilities. For a map of our beautiful college see here
Cloisters Chapel Gardens Clore Music Studios JCR Cloisters We have one of the most beautiful cloisters in Oxford, the earliest in origination and enclosed in design (i.e. it does not go anywhere). It is a good environment for contemplation, admiration, and photogeny with the tree filmed in the fourth Harry Potter film.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
