<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MCR Services on New College MCR</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MCR Services on New College MCR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welfare</title>
      <link>/services/welfare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/welfare/</guid>
      <description>Nothing brightens than a surprise bit of chocolate in your pidge. Chocolate Fairy.
Table of Contents
 MCR Support  Peer Supporters Sexual Health Support   College Support  SCR Welfare Team Medical welfare Porters    MCR Support Peer Supporters Irene Yang
irene.yang@ndorms.ox.ac.uk
I am in my second year of a DPhil in Musculoskeletal Science looking at just the outer halves of each knee. I spend most of my time in Headingtonbut when I’m not there, I’m in the MCR, or writing, painting, sketching or taking photos of nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Support</title>
      <link>/services/emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/emergency/</guid>
      <description>Nothing is scarier than having an emergency and being short on money, or having a broken bike or a laptop.
 Bike Borrowing Scheme Emergency Laptop Borrowing Scheme  How to get them Conditions   Solidarity Fund Emergency Funding  Bike Borrowing Scheme Emergency Laptop Borrowing Scheme How to get them Email college IT helpdesk@new.ox.ac.uk and ask for the the emergency laptops. Depending on the time and day, you will be able to swing by IT, or they will prepare them and leave them at the lodge for you to collect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Life</title>
      <link>/services/social/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/social/</guid>
      <description>Each term, the MCR offers various events for members to come together. You can learn about these events on our Facebook page or via email (see here for details).
 MCR Events  Exchange Dinners Guest Nights Second Desserts BOPs Karaoke Nights Tastings Garden Party   Organize your own event  MCR Events A list of upcoming MCR events can be found on our MCR calendar (teams link).
Exchange Dinners These are occasions in which around 15 MCR members go to another college to have dinner with their MCR in one week, as well as host them at our college in another week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports</title>
      <link>/services/sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/sports/</guid>
      <description>New College has one of the largest sports grounds in Oxford, and they are conveniently located just behind the pavilion.
All you need to know, from croquet to e-Sports Sports are a vital part of college life at New in general and for the MCR in particular, since our common room (located at the Sports Pavilion) is right beside the college&amp;rsquo;s Sports Ground.
Whether you are a seasoned sport enthusiast or a newbie, we hope that you will make good use of the facilities and equipment available to you for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bar</title>
      <link>/services/bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/bar/</guid>
      <description>We have the (arguably) cheapest bar in Oxford, run by the community, always providing a good time as well as a wide variety of alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages.
Opening Hours The bar opens regularly Wednesdays and Saturdays, and after various special events.
Price List Price List
Become a volunteer You’ve sampled our abundant collection of drinks, but feel like you still have more to contribute?
… Then sign-up to be a MCR bar volunteer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Borrowing</title>
      <link>/services/borrowing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/borrowing/</guid>
      <description>The MCR own various items that can be borrowed by members, like bikes, instruments, board games or books.
Bikes The MCR owns a fleet of bicycles which MCR members can borrow for a few days at a time for free! These are maintained by the MCR Bike Rep, so feel free to reach out with any questions.
If you would like to borrow a bike, you must first fill out this form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pavilion </title>
      <link>/services/pavilion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/pavilion/</guid>
      <description>Our MCR Pavillion is a beautiful building for any student of the MCR to enjoy at any moment&amp;rsquo;s notice! Our MCR facilities are one of the few common rooms that are fully accessible, containing a common space with a bar and our TV room.
 The Spoom TV room Accessibility  The Spoom Our main share space is the &amp;ldquo;Rew Nooner Spoom&amp;rdquo;, named after our former warden Reverend Spooner. Here, you will find fellow members drinking till closing time on the bi-weekly bar nights on Wed and Fri (more drinking details here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equality and Diversity</title>
      <link>/services/ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/ed/</guid>
      <description>Who to ask for help? Each of us are unique in circumstances, personality, upbringing, and nature. If you ever feel the need to discuss any ranging issue pertaining to equality and diversity that is important to you, we encourage you to reach out to any member of the Greater-Equality&amp;amp;Diversity team!
 Our Equality and Diversity rep: Mandisa Shandu (mandisa.shandu@new.ox.ac.uk) Our Women&amp;rsquo;s Officer: Eleanor Lischka (eleanor.lischka@new.ox.ac.uk) Our LGBTIAQ+ rep: Tom Sweeney (thomas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Punting</title>
      <link>/services/punt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/punt/</guid>
      <description>Ahoy, intrepid sailors and fearless canalfarers! It is your Vice Admiral of Punts speaking.
Introduction to punting New College owns a glorious fleet of FIVE punts that can be used during Trinity term by every member of college, including associate members.
Knowing the instructions on how to use the punts is not only tremendously helpful, it is also a mandatory requirement to punt at New College.
If you have never punted before, make the most of your New College membership and give it a try!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democracy</title>
      <link>/services/democracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/democracy/</guid>
      <description>In the MCR we are as democratic as we can and provide opportunities to have your voice be heard.
 General Meetings Elections  Non-Executive Elections Executive Elections   Constitution  General Meetings General Meetings are the essence of base democracy. Held once a term, they are an opportunity for any member of the MCR to submit motions asking for money to be spend on something, changes to be made to the constitution or stances to be taken.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>